

Abhishek Gautam

UI UX Designer

Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh officialabhishekgautam@gmail.com

Profile

Accomplished UI UX Designer with 2+ years of experience, specialized in visuals & branding eager to add some gradients to this world with my Artform.

Currently working as a UI UX Designer at Carnegie Tech LLP (crypto-based startup). Also having experience in Graphic designing and development using Web Technologies besides a stunning portfolio worked with Several clients & collaboration with Dev & Marketing team.

Work Experience

UI UX Designer at Carnegie Tech LLP

May 2021 - Present

<u>Carnegie Tech LLP</u> is a Crypto Startup company, focuses on providing technology support for DEFI projects.

- · user research and designing user flow for UI
- designing logos, illustrations for the web & other social media assets for marketing.
- designing visually aesthetic & responsive UI for both Web & mob using Adobe XD/ Figma.
- · collaborating effectively with the marketing and dev team.

• Freelancing as Graphic Designer

2019 - Present

Education

 Bachelor of Technology, <u>Guru Tegh Bahadur Institute of</u> <u>Technology</u>, New Delhi

August 2018 - Present

Information Technology

Percentage: 71.288 %

12th, Holy Public School, Agra

March 2017 - March 2018

Percentage: 82 %

10th, <u>Holy Public School</u>, Agra

March 2015 - March 2016

CGPA: 10

Social Links

- Facebook
- Instagram

Portfolio Links

- Be Behance
- **G** Github

Skills

Adobe XD

Figma

Adobe Illustrator

Prototyping

Wireframing

HTML

CSS Frameworks

JS

Python

Courses & Certifications

Fundamentals of Graphic Design CalArts, Coursera

4 Weeks, July 2020

verify here

Python Data Structure

University of Michigan, Coursera

4 Weeks, March 2021

verify here

Interests

Finance

Cooking

Art

Projects

MY MANDI - Doorstep delivery service

Illustration | Landing Page UI | Splash Screen

My Mandi provides fresh vegetables and essentials delivery at your doorstep. It was a part of the freelance project.

SAFECHAIN - crypto wallet

Illustration | UI UX

<u>SafeChain</u> is non-custodial crypto wallet to store private keys and other sensitive information across blockchains. Worked on it during my internship.

COVID ESSENTIALS

App UI UX | Interaction Design

<u>Covid Essentials</u> is an all-in-one app for all covid essentials in one place. Mockup is also made in Adobe XD. It was a part of a personal project.

SOLSHIBA - Doge theme Crypto Currency

UI UX | Illustration

<u>Solshiba</u> is a dog themed crypto token website similar to the famous doge coin. an all-in-one app for all covid essentials in one place. Mockup is also made in Adobe XD.

COACHING PROFESSIONAL WEBSITE - using Tailwind CSS

Frontend | Web Design

Fully responsive website made using frontend framework "Tailwind CSS" & Alpine JS. It was a part of personal project. Check the live website deployed on <u>Github Pages</u>.

• PERSONAL PORTFOLIO WEBSITE - using HTML CSS JS

Frontend | Responsive Design

Fully responsive website made only using HTML CSS & JS no frameworks used. It is a part of personal project showcasing my designing & development portfolio. Check the live website deployed on <u>Github Pages.</u>

Behance

Check out my complete portfolio on **Behance** focused on visuals & branding.